( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
He would die for his country
without hesitation,
yet when it comes to Miss Lin,
he is endlessly imperfect
and full of helplessness.
They were destined to meet,
but not to be together.
With all my heart,
I pray to all the deities and Buddhas
that Mr. Shen and Miss Lin
meet again in the days to come.
May they meet and not forget each other,
continuing their love in the next life.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=Episode 28=
(Echoes of Gang City)
Have the cargo ship to Gang City
deliver this letter
to Shuyi in your name.
You must hide your identity.
Do not expose yourself.
Understood.
Qianmo, here!
Right here.
Mr. Shen instructed
that you must bring
back news of Miss Lin.
I will.
I'm leaving now.
It's a must.
Hurry up.
Miss Lin!
Miss Lin.
Is there any news of Mr. Zhou?
Miss!
- Miss!
- Madam Liu?
Madam Liu, why are you here?
There is a letter for you.
(To Miss Lin)
Who... Who gave this to you?
It was Qianmo. Qianmo gave it to you.
(Miss, under Mr. Zhou's guidance,)
(I have made progress in my schoolwork.)
(But for some reason, Mr. Zhou
hasn't come to class for a week.)
(It's really giving me a headache.)
It's Shen Gu's handwriting.
This is bad.
We must evacuate this place immediately.
- Miss Lin went missing in Gang City.
- Miss...
We tried everything
and finally contacted her.
But it was still too late.
Miss Lin sacrificed herself
to protect the comrades' evacuation.
Shen Gu passed away.
Mr. Shen was also murdered.
Mr. Shen and Miss Lin never
found their happy ending, even in death.
Grandfather,
have you told me this story before?
When you were little and sick,
you always pestered me
to tell you stories.
So I just took those past events
and slowly told them to you as stories.
No wonder.
No wonder I always have this dream.
Don't cry.
Shen Gu.
Grandfather.
Where is your jade pendant?
Right here.
This is the jade pendant
I lost in Gang City all those years ago.
Not only did it save your life,
but it also saved mine.
Today, you are standing together.
Perhaps this is
another kind of fulfillment.
(To Shen Gu)
To Shen Gu.
This is the last letter
Miss Lin gave to Mr. Shen.
When the nation is restored,
we shall wed.
(From your wife, Shuyi)
She knew,
right?
From now on, I'm leaving Minghui to you.
No matter what happens,
never forget the spirit of Minghui.
Create for the people,
and serve the prosperity of the nation.
Grandfather,
don't worry.
We will cherish this memory.
Grandfather, I'm sorry.
During this time,
we made you worry.
It's good
that you're back.
Dad,
before I propose to Wanxin,
I still wanted to ask for your consent.
(Tomb of Beloved Father, Xu Zhaoming)
The project you developed
was very successful.
It even saved Qingniao.
I promise you
that I will love her,
protect her, and respect her,
just as you did.
And I'll let her always be herself.
Don't worry.
(Grave of Loving Father, Xu Zhaoming)
How are the preparations for tonight?
Don't worry about it.
Well, you're on your own this time.
Don't be too nervous.
Why aren't you talking?
If you're not talking, you're nervous.
What do you need me to do?
Just say the word.
I need you to stay out of it.
Okay.
Are you still thinking about
the story Grandfather told?
Do you think
there's an afterlife?
If there is an afterlife,
we will meet again.
Then, I will recognize you first.
All right.
Let's make a promise.
Before you arrive,
I will always wait for you.
It's a deal.
If there is an afterlife.
Come with me, Wanxin.
Why did you bring me here?
Ms. Xu Wanxin,
are you willing to spend
the rest of your life with me?
I am.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
(To Shen Gu)
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
Mr. Shen,
a letter has come from Gang City.
Miss Lin has replied.
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
(When the nation is restored,
we shall wed. From your wife, Shuyi)
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪
(Shen Hao is convicted of kidnapping,
intentional injury, and insider trading,)
(sentenced to 15 years in prison for
combined crimes, and fined 25 million.)
(Shen Tingyuan, is convicted of insider trading,
sentenced to 5 years and 5 months,)
(and fined 10 million.)
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪Blending with letters left unread
drifting through the air♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears
quietly appear♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪So many questions time itself
could not make clear♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪Every dream I had became something
I want with you near♪
♪How many letters have I written
just for you?♪
♪If only you could truly hear
what my heart is trying to say♪
♪From this life on
no distance could keep us apart♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled
one day♪
♪But I want more
than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending
we face?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you
will hear it all♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪